right to publish out of hero image and thumbnail image so switch this so that you can see again
and right away it loaded all of them and it shows you the shape events since these are kind of small
just so that it is easier for you to um recognize which is which when you apply these little buttons
which are the roles um and then i also just updated it so that it shows a preview of the
original file name um because as you can see i had already planned out which one was gonna be
the thumbnail so i can see thumbnail right there and hero so i can push hero right there
just in the matter just because of time so gallery calorie calorie
one of these there we go checkout now so mine were already cropped from something else it still will
compress them and turn them into web web web webp it's the super compressed type of uh image form
it's super compressed type of uh image form
but if they weren't cropped so a checkout would make it square there's a square image
all of the uh gallery images and the hero are all four by five and then the thumbnail is like a
standard um um so that would be 16 by nine so it's standard uh i mean if they're larger it will
take a little longer because it's going through the whole process with each one it's uh you know
cropping it and then downsizing it and then uploading it to this cdn the content delivery
network so that it just gets a url link so that the website loads quickly and then it puts that
in the database and then does the next one so it is doing a bunch of things there we go so yeah
and then this you can click and drag to reorder them say i wanted him to go first if you go in
here that's where you could delete images and then upload different ones but it doesn't let
you publish the first time because it's going to make you preview before you publish anything
so we'll just preview that and you can see all of the automatically populated text up here
and then i also just fixed these so that it shows the accurate image right there you can hide those
details and then go through all of the pictures cool so that's it i mean like i said i'm going
to send you the test urls so you can play around and um yeah there won't really be much
there'll be like two urls and the real one you already know um and then just a note that once
you're ready like after i would i would give chat gbt one or two little tries just make sure that
you are comfortable with it and then once you let me know all i have to do is swap out one little
url um yeah so that's it please look it over give me all types of feedback i hope you like
it but yes anything you want to change we can totally change i'm happy to do that